Guide to the Nell Irvin Painter Papers, 1793-2021 and undated, bulk 1876-2007 RL.00990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials Series, 1810-2007 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Personal Images, 1900-2007 and undated, 13 boxes
    - 1995, at Camilla Michele's house, Donna Fay from FCRS (Box 277)
    - 1996 Feb., UCRS Convention Alburquerque, MN (Box 277)
    - 1997 Mar., Snapshots of Dona Irvin (Box 277)
    - 1997 Mar., Pictures of Dona (Box 277)
    - 1997, Frank and Dona Irvin (Box 277)
    - 1997, Ro and Gerda, Nell and Glenn's cats (Box 277)
    - 1997, 2002, 60th and 65th wedding anniversary celebration of Frank and Dona Irvin (Box 277)
    - 1998-1999, NIP, friends and family (Box 277)
    - 1998-1999, Ro and Gerda, NIP's cats (Box 277)
    - 1999 Mar., Frank and Irvin's surprise birthday party (Box 277)
    - 1999 July 7, Dona's birthday dinner at La Belle Creak Restaurant in Emeryville, Calif. (Box 277)
    - 1999, Family of Charles McGruder (Box 277)
    - 1999, Raymond family snapshots (Box 277)
    - 1999, Snapshots of friends and family (Box 277)
    - 2000 Apr., Unidentified man (Box 277)
    - 2000 June, Dennis Shafer (Box 277)
    - 2000 Oct., Phil, Frank, and Dona, E. Charleston, Ver. (Box 277)
    - 2000, Family and friends (Box 277)
    - 2000, Snapshot of Kevin (Box 277)
    - 2002 Jan., Frank's birthday party (Box 277)
    - 2002, New Jersey Council for the Humanities (Box 277)
    - 2002, "The Family" First Church of Religious Science (Box 277)
    - 2002-2005, NIP, family and friends (Box 277)
    - 2003 Oct. 16, Dona Irvin snapshots (Box 277)
    - 2004, Phil's birthday in San Antonio, TX (Box 278)
    - 2004, Frank and Dona in San Antonio, TX (Box 278)
    - 2004, Tech High Reunion, Class of 1959 (Box 278)
    - 2005, 68th anniversary celebration, 2 folders (Box 278)
    - 2006, and undated, Various snapshots, friends (Box 278)
    - 2007 Oct. 4, Nell Irvin Painter Day, city of Boston (Box 278)
    - Undated, Family, various snapshots (Box 278)
    - Undated, Family and friends snapshots (Box 278)
    - Undated, Frank and Dona Irvin and others (Box 278)
    - Undated, Friends (Box 278)
    - Undated, Protest/rally "Defend the Monroe North Carolina Victims" (Box 278)
    - Undated, Reunion of Frank's Boys and Girls from University of California, Berkeley (Box 278)
    - Undated, Reunion photos, Dona and Frank (Box 278)
    - Undated, Unidentified couple (Box 278)
    - Undated, Unidentified family (Box 278)
    - Undated, Various people (Box 278)
    - Undated, Yusufu Yunsa (Box 278)
  - Large Prints
    Prints, mainly 8x10 inches, were separated from the three photographic materials subseries in order to provide flat storage. Some smaller related prints, especially older ones, are housed with these. For more information about intellectual content, consult the respective subseries notes above. Some materials were damaged by water.
    - Writings and Research Images, 1864-2001 and undated
      - 1864-1937, Cotton and sugar cane workers, Kansas migrants, political posters, and other subjects (Box 232)
      - 1866 and undated, Reproductions from the University of Texas Archives (Box 232)
      - 1867-1870 and undated, Railroad posters, including Kansas-Pacific and Union-Pacific (Box 232)
      - 1877-1907 and undated, Research for Exodusters, reproduced from the Kansas State Historical Society, Library of Congress, and unidentified sources, 10 black-and-white prints, water-damaged (Box 232)
      - 1880-1906 and undated, Negro troops and cowboys; Nicodemus posters and settlers (Box 232)
      - 1888, Negro homesteaders, Nebraska (Box 232)
      - 1937 and undated, Birmingham, Ala. coalminers and steelworks, tenant houses, and other reproductions from the Library of Congress (Box 232)
      - 1994 Apr. 29, Virginian Luxuries, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation, Williamsburg, Va. (Box 232)
      - 2001, Reproduction from Peabody Museum, Harvard University (Box 232)
      - Undated, Photograph of Sojourner Truth (Box 232)
    - Professional Service Images, 1982-2007
      - 1982 Nov., NIP speaking at AFT Convention (Box 232)
      - 1983 Feb., NIP portrait for Black History Month presentation (Box 232)
      - 1985 Jul., Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China group photo (Box 232)
      - 1992 Sept.-Oct., Frontline, Clarence Thomas and Anita Hill, one year anniversary confirmation hearings (Box 232)
      - 2004, Hallinan Consulting, TCA Event (Box 232)
      - 2007, "Creating Black Americans," presentation sponsored by Ruth Love, Oakland, CA (Box 278)
      - 2007 Mar., Organization of American History (Box 279)
    - Personal Images, 1905-2007 and undated
      - Circa 1972, Ken, portrait (Box 232)
      - 1981 Sept., NIP portrait with note from David Williamson (Box 232)
      - Circa 1991, NIP, publicity portraits (Box 232)
      - 1996, NIP at Wesleyan University commencement (Box 232)
      - 2000, NIP portraits (Box 232)
      - Undated, Woman, unidentified, in black-and-white portrait (Box 232)
      - 1905-1963 and undated, Family photographs including Frank and Dona (Box 279)
      - 1942 and undated, McGruder and Donato families (Box 279)
      - 1942 and undated, McGruder and Donato families (Box 279)
      - 1947, 1962, Portraits of Nell Painter (Box 279)
      - 1965 and undated, Portraits--Nell, Frank, and Dona (Box 279)
      - 1981-1982, Frank running races (Box 279)
      - 1981, 1997-1999, 2007, Portraits--Nell, Frank, and Dona (Box 279)
      - 1982, Retirement party (Box 279)
      - 1985 or 1986, Portrait of Nell Painter for Standing at Armageddon (Box 279)
      - 1996, Portrait of Guadalupe Copendah, signed (Box 279)
      - 2002-2006 and undated, Miscellaneous portraits and snapshots of family and friends (Box 279)
  - Negatives
    Format group consisting of negatives generally related to the three photographic materials subseries. Many of the negatives were housed separately when received and cannot be matched item-for-item to the prints without extensive further work. For more information about intellectual content, consult the respective subseries notes above..
    - Writings and Research Images, 1976-1979 and undated (Box 233)
    - Professional Service, 1984 (Box 233)
    - Personal Images, 1970-1989 and undated (Box 233)
    - 1961, negatives from travel and family visits in the Bay Area, California, 12 folders of strips and 7 rolls (Box 295)
  - Photograph Albums
    Albums contain images and ephemera documenting the personal lives of Painter and her family and friends. Some albums were disbound for preservation reasons; these are housed upright in the main subseries above, with their album source indicated as part of the folder title.
    - Dona Irvin, book party, 2002 (Box 280)
    - Frank and Dona Irvin, 60th and 63rd anniversaries 1997, 2000, 3 items (Box 280)
    - Frank Irvin, 80th birthday, 1999 (Box 280)
    - Glenn Shafer, 60th birthday, 2006, 2 items (Box 280)
    - Thad Davis, Maine, 1998 (Box 280)
    - Frank and Dona Irvin, 65th anniversary, 2002, 2 items (Box 281)
    - Frank and Dona Irvin, 70th anniversary ("70 years of Lovin'"), 2007, 2 items (Box 281)
    - John and Kary Sanders, wedding, 1983 (Box 281)
    - Phil's birthdays, 1992-1994, 3 items (Box 281)
    - Dona Irvin, 84th birthday, 2001 (Box 282)
    - Frank Irvin, 85th birthday and reunion of his "boys and girls," 2004, 3 items (Box 282)
    - Glacier Park trip,1984 (Box 282)
    - Irvin Family, "Wonderful Happenings 1992," 1992 (Box 282)
    - Irvin house, dinner party, 1987 (Box 282)
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1968-2006 and undated, 9 boxes
  Audio and video recordings made by or about Painter, including interviews she conducted as part of research and interviews of her on various television programs. Arranged in two subseries by format: Audio Materials and Video Materials. Total running time (TRT) is shown in parentheses if known.
  [Originals closed to use. Use copies for most audio items are available in the collection. Otherwise, Technical Services staff must arrange to have use copy made. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
  - Audio Materials Subseries, 1968-2002 and undated, 8 boxes
    Contains mainly interviews, some conducted by Painter and some from other sources, and a few recordings of Painter's speaking engagements. Recording formats consist of reel to reel tapes, audiocassettes, and compact discs. Arranged chronologically within each format.
    [Originals closed to use. Use copies are available for all recordings except 56AB, 57AB, and 58, which can be made on request. Preservation and use copies for all format groupings are housed together and are listed at the end of the subseries.]
    - Audio Tapes, Originals OR1-OR2
      - OR1. 1968 Dec., Teenage Booktalk: Journey Toward Freedom, by Jacqueline Bernard; recorded at Powell Library, Dec. 15; broadcast on WNYC, Dec. 23; Reel No. G53 (TRT unknown), 1/4" tape, 7" reel (Box 234)
      - OR2. Undated, Living Atlanta: The Atlanta University Complex. Program One: An Enclave of Black Intelligentsia in a Segregated Society, Reel 1 of 1 (TRT 30:06), 1/4" tape, 5" reel (Box 234)
    - Audiocassettes, Originals OR3-OR33, OR56-OR58
      - OR3. 1971 Oct. 17, Poplar Grove (Missionary) Baptist Church, Humboldt, Kan., morning service (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR4. 1971 Oct. 17, Poplar Grove Baptist Church, Humboldt, Kan., morning service and first part of anniversary service for Rev. Baynham, afternoon (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR5. 1971 Oct. 17, Poplar Grove Baptist Church, Humboldt, Kan., parts 2 and 3 of anniversary service, afternoon (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR6. 1971 Oct. 17, Poplar Grove Baptist Church, Humboldt, Kan., anniversary service for Rev. R.L. Baynham of Poplar Grove and 2nd Baptist Church of Iola; Rev. L.V. Wake of New Hope Baptist Church, Parsons, Kan.(TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR7. 1971 Oct. 19, Mr. Alfred Landon, Topeka, Kan. (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR8. circa 1971 Oct., Mrs. Gertrude Stovall, history of Humboldt, Kan.; Poplar Grove Baptist Church anniversary service (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR9. 1972 Jan. 29, Irva and Andrew Charleston, Prairie View (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR10A-C. 1972 Mar.-May, 3 cassettes
        - OR10A-B. 1972 May 14, Mrs. Anna Smith (mother, b. 1865) and Mrs. Gertrude Watts (b. 1894) (TRT unknown), 2 cassettes (Box 234)
        - OR10C. 1972 Mar. 13, Greenville Delta Democrat Times; Mrs. Smith and Mrs. Edna Johnson, friend (TRT unknown) (Box 234)
      - OR11A-C. 1972 Apr. 19, Mr. H. R. Wilson, Mother Bethel, Philadelphia (TRT unknown), 3 cassettes (Box 234)
      - OR12A-B. 1975 Feb. 22, Mrs. Marie B. Frazier, Washington D.C., Series B (TRT unknown), 2 cassettes (Box 235)
      - OR13A-B. 1977 Mar. 23, American Views of Blood, Class, and Civilization in the South at the Turn of the Century, Charles Warren Center (TRT unknown), 2 cassettes (Box 235)
      - OR14A-B. 1977 Apr., Donna and Frank's Anniversary [Painter's parents] (TRT unknown), 2 cassettes (Box 235)
      - OR15. 1978 Oct. 16, Hosea Hudson (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR16A-B. 1980 July 12, Rayford Logan (TRT unknown), 2 cassettes (Box 235)
      - OR17. 1982 May 6, Katherine Dupre Lumpkin, Chapel Hill, N.C. (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR18. 1988 Feb. 22, Langston Hughes, National Public Radio (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR19. 1988 Apr. 15, Marvel Cooke, New York City (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR20. 1988 Apr. 27, Franklin Williams, New York City (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR21. 1988 Apr. 27, Gloster Current, New York City (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR22. 1988 Aug. 10, Loyal Garner Jr. case, National Public Radio (TRT 15:00) (Box 235)
      - OR23. 1993 Feb. 12, Sojourner Truth on WBAI radio (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR24. 1994 Sept. 12, Protect Historic America: The Cradle of Democracy: Virginia's Historic Piedmont (TRT 88:00) (Box 235)
      - OR25. 1994, Black Women in America (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR26. 1995 Jun. 13, Going North (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR27. 1996 Jan. 17, African American Women in the Suffrage Movement, Iowa State University (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR28. 1996 Feb. 27, Gutman Memorial Lecture (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR29. 1996 Sep. 19, "Monitor Radio: The Broadcast Edition of The Christian Science Monitor" (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR30. 1996 Oct. 17, McGinty (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR31A-C. 1997, Soundings from the National Humanities Center: Side A, Sojourner & Frederick (NIP and John Sekora) (TRT unknown), 3 copies (Box 235)
      - OR32. 1997, Soundings from the National Humanities Center: Side A, Sojourner & Frederick (NIP and John Sekora); Side B, Culture and Work (David Smith and William Julius Wilson) (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR33. 2002 Apr. 28, The Sojourner Truth Story, Mt. Carmel Baptist Church, Washington D.C. (TRT unknown) (Box 235)
      - OR56A. 1997 Aug. 2, "Frank and Dona Irvin's 60th Anniversary Celebration" (Box 290)
      - OR56B. "Frank and Dona Irvin's 60th Anniversary Celebration" (Box 290)
      - OR57A. 2002 Apr. 20, "Frank and Dona Irvin's 65th Anniversary", tape 1, Church of Religious Science, Oakland, CA (Box 290)
      - OR57B. 2002 Apr. 20, "Frank and Dona Irvin's 65th Anniversary", tape 2, Church of Religious Science, Oakland, CA (Box 290)
      - OR58. Untitled, undated (Box 290)
    - Compact Discs, Originals, OR34, undated
      - OR34. Undated, Songs of Sojourner, produced by The Truth Project, Inc.; from the play The Trials of Sojourner Truth, by Steve Gottlieb and Gillian Farrell (Box 234)
    - Audio Materials, Preservation Copies
      - Preservation copies PC1-PC18, PC34 (Box 236)
      - Preservation copies PC19-PC33 (Box 237)
    - Audio Materials, Use Copies
      - Use copies UC1-UC18, UC34 (Box 238)
      - Use copies UC19-UC33 (Box 239)
  - Video Materials Subseries, 1987-2006 and undated, 3 boxes
    Contains tapes of Painter's speaking engagements, interviews of her on programs from C-SPAN and other sources, and various commercial or academic productions with which she was involved. Recording formats consist of VHS videocassettes and digital video discs (DVD). Arranged chronologically within each format.
    [Originals closed to use. Technical Services staff must arrange to have use copy made on request. Please contact Research Services staff before coming to use the collection.]
    - Videocassettes, Originals OR35-OR54, OR59-OR67
      - OR35. 1987 Mar., Rock and Roll (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR36. 1993 Feb. 4, How Do We Know What We Know of Sojourner Truth? (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR37. 1996 Mar. 14, Women's History Month: Sojourner Truth: The Life of a Symbol, Trenton State College (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR38. 1996 Sep. 24, Sojourner Truth, The Making of a Symbol (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR39A-B. 1996 Oct. 22, Booknotes: Nell Irvin Painter, C-SPAN (TRT 60:00), 2 copies (Box 240)
      - OR40. 1996, United States History: Origins-WWII Volume 10: Reconstruction and Segregation 1865-1910, Schlessinger Video Productions (TRT 35:00) (Box 240)
      - OR41. 1996, United States History: Origins-WWII Volume 14: The Progressive Movement, Schlessinger Video Productions (TRT 35:00) (Box 240)
      - OR42. 1996, United States History: Origins-WWII Volume 16: The Great War, Schlessinger Video Productions (TRT 35:00) (Box 240)
      - OR43. 1997 Jan. 24, Shattering the Silences, PBS (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR44A-C. 1997 Sep. 1, Washington Journal: NIP and Sylvia Morns, C-SPAN (TRT 67:48), 3 copies (Box 240)
      - OR45. 2000 Nov. 10, Ralph Bunche: An American Odyssey, William Greaves Productions, Inc. (TRT unknown) (Box 240)
      - OR46. 2003 Jan. 29, The Rise and Fall of Jim Crow, Episode 1: Promises Betrayed 1865-1896, WNET, N.Y. (TRT 57:00) (Box 241)
      - OR47. 2003 Jan. 29, The Rise and Fall of Jim Crow, Episode 2: Fighting Back 1896-1917, WNET, N.Y. (TRT 57:00) (Box 241)
      - OR48. 2003 Jan. 29, The Rise and Fall of Jim Crow, Episode 3: Don't Shout Too Soon 1918-1940, WNET, N.Y. (TRT 57:00) (Box 241)
      - OR49. 2003 Jan. 29, The Rise and Fall of Jim Crow, Episode 4: Terror and Triumph 1940-1954, WNET, N.Y. (TRT 57:00) (Box 241)
      - OR50. 2005 Jun. 1, Professor Nell Irvin Painter, WNET, N.Y. (TRT unknown) (Box 241)
      - OR51. Undated, The Greatest Trials of All Times: Scottsboro Boys, Cinetel Productions (TRT unknown) (Box 241)
      - OR52. Undated, NIP--Jefferson Community College, Watertown, N.Y. (TRT unknown) (Box 241)
      - OR53. Undated, "'Reflections' on Mary Mebane's Mary," Cathy Stowe, moderator; with Professors Earl S. Thorpe, NIP, and David Lewis (TRT unknown) (Box 241)
      - OR54. Undated, Ron Brown (TRT unknown) (Box 241)
      - OR59. 1993 May 9, Black Renaissance featuring Dona Irvin (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR60. 1993 May 12, WAVE '93 alumnae resources (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR61. 1993 Nov. 4, Unsung Heart of Black America, Dona L. Irvin, University of Houston (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR62. 1994 Sept. 20, Unsung Heart of Black America, Dona Irvin, "Wee Poets" TV program, Oakland, CA (TRT 28:40) (Box 290)
      - OR63. 1997 Sept. 30, The Oprah Winfrey Show, "Funny Love Stories," Frank and Dona Irvin (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR64. 1997 Oct. 4, "Abdoul Doumbia, drummer from Mali, West Africa" (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR65. 1999 Jan. 4, "Family Shield- Keeping a Marriage Working," (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR66. 2002 Apr. 20, "Frank and Dona 65th anniversary," (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
      - OR67. 2006 Nov. 14, "Nell Painter- Prize," (TRT unknown) (Box 290)
    - DVDs, Original OR55
      - OR55. 2005 Sep. 22, The American Experience, with Nell Irvin Painter on "The Age of Realism," Prentice Hall/Pearson Education (TRT unknown), DVD (Box 241)
- Electronic Formats Series, 1986-2007 and undated
  Digital files, mostly unidentified beyond general categories. It is likely that most of this material is already represented in the collection in printed form. Consists mainly of correspondence and drafts of writings by Painter, including material associated with her books Standing at Armageddon: The United States, 1877-1919 (1987), Sojourner Truth, A Life, A Symbol (1996), and Creating Black Americans (2005). Arranged in order in which disks were received and numbered; disks 026-142, received in Accession 2008-0016, have been grouped by format, but otherwise arranged as received. Unnumbered diskettes may also appear in Accession 2010-0116, listed at the end of this inventory.
  [FURTHER PROCESSING NEEDED BEFORE USE: Files for 012-025 have been migrated to a library file server; contact Research Services staff for access. Disks 001-011 are unreadable at present. Disks 026-142 have not been migrated. All original disks have been retained in collection, box 296.]
  - Diskettes
    - Disk001. NYU, NYUM, 1987 May, NYPL, 1987 Feb., Fempress, 1986 Sept. (Box 241)
    - Disk002. Minhists.lon, Minhists.med, Minhists.sho, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk003. Avos.65, 1987 Mar. (Box 241)
    - Disk004. Armageddon #4, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk005. Armageddon #3, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk006. Armageddon #2, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk007. Armageddon #1, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk008. Avos.65.3, with notes, 1865.3LO, 1865.3SH, without notes, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk009. Gutman.LH, Gutman.WD, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk010. Journal.F87, Journal.1881, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk011. Painter Minhists.Lon, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk012. Painter's CV, 1998 May (Box 241)
    - Disk013. White, 1992 Jan. 8 (Box 241)
    - Disk014. Various Files, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk015. Sojourner (various files), undated (Box 241)
    - Disk016. SENT.OCT and various files, 1994 (Box 241)
    - Disk017. Copy of MS. Sent tp Sheedy and Barber, 1994 Aug. 29 (Box 241)
    - Disk018. Sojourner/Notes (and many misc. notes), 1994 Feb. (Box 241)
    - Disk019. Sojourner/Notes, 1994 Feb. (Box 241)
    - Disk020. Sojourner (Notes and Book), 1994 Feb. (Box 241)
    - Disk021. Book Chapters and various files, 1993 Sep. (Box 241)
    - Disk022. various files, undated (Box 241)
    - Disk023. Sojourner Notes, 1992 Fall (Box 241)
    - Disk024. ACLS History E-Book Project, Master Page Images, Scholarly Publishing Office, University of Michigan, 2004 Mar. 31 (Box 241)
    - Disk025. ACLS History E-Book Project, PDF and SGM, Scholarly Publishing Office, University of Michigan, 2004 Mar. 31 (Box 241)
    - Diskettes, 3.5"
      - Disk026. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk027. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk028. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk029. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk030. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk031. Various files, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk032. Timelines, chaps 6-10, 2002 Summer (Box 241)
      - Disk033. Same Nell x1100.jpg, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk034. Black Faculty, Black Studies, 2000 Nov (Box 241)
      - unspecified (Box 241)
      - Disk035. Huggins Lectures, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk036. EGCT Essay Backup, Robeson, Griffler, Palmer, Essay RE2, Perry.Rev, Carby.87, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk037. Goldfield, Herbhill, Letter.I, Negro.TH, Knit reading, JWH, Berks, Letter (Yale), undated (Box 241)
      - Disk038. Draft of S.T. sent to EB, A:\Sent.10, A:\Draft.12, A:Chap 12, 1994 Aug. (Box 241)
      - Disk039. Letter, Journal.882, Journal.883/884/885/891, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk040. Claudia Tate, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk041. Courses, 2003 Spring (Box 241)
      - Disk042. HIS 581, disk full, 2000 Feb. (Box 241)
      - Disk043. Email, 1995 Jan.-Mar. (Box 241)
      - Disk044. Richard Wright, 1995 Oct. (Box 241)
      - Disk045. Dissertation reports, Hist 465.95, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk046. Sent, 1995, Sept. (Box 241)
      - Disk047. Sojourner\Notes (Rochester), Sojourner\Notes\AAS, disk full, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk048. CAS BS, Culpeper grants applications, on writing, Charley email 2-4 1994, Robin Kelley, Nellie, Glenn, email, 1994 (Box 241)
      - Disk049. Princeton /Grad, /Afam311.93, /Hist 465.94, handouts, 1993 Fall (Box 241)
      - Disk050. Leo Frank and Industry, Hist 351.95 grades, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk051. Hist 400.94, Rider.95, 1992, 1995 (Box 241)
      - Disk052. Hist 381, Spr 1995, photos: TVA workers, Norris dam, Sojourner Truth C-D-V, Sojourner Truth cameo, 1995 (Box 241)
      - Disk053. Sojourner.MI, Princeton 381.92, 1992 Apr. (Box 241)
      - Disk054. Whiteness packet, working syllabus, 1998 Nov. (Box 241)
      - Disk055. Whiteness course, spring 1999, Disk #3 Mar. Apr., 1999 (Box 241)
      - Disk056. Whiteness course, disk 1 1999 Spring (Box 241)
      - Disk057. Whiteness course, disk 2, 1999 Spring (Box 241)
      - Disk058. Toshiba files, Keddie Brown, current sexuality notes, Sojourner notes AAS 311.94, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk059. ABWH, GA Hist + notes, sexuality, Tappan, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk060. Princeton/381.92, /Grad, /589.90, /Men, /SR Theses, 1992 Oct. (Box 241)
      - Disk061. E-mail, 1993 fall, 1994 spring (Box 241)
      - Disk062. Princeton\AFAM files, 311.91, Grad, 384, Misc, 500, 1992 Oct. (Box 241)
      - Disk063. Anna's version of Nell's versions, 1999 Aug. (Box 241)
      - Disk064. ABWH, AF-A-M, AF-AM/500, CASH, Current, Glenn, Journal, 1992 Oct. (Box 241)
      - Disk065. #5, His 382, 1999 Apr. (Box 241)
      - Disk066. Whiteness course #4, 1999 (Box 241)
      - Disk067. Rutgers files, JAH files, 1992 Fall (Box 241)
      - Disk068. Narrative, 7.EDS, undated (Box 241)
      - Disk069. A/Editor, A/Essays, A/Reviews, A:\Princeton\Hist 381.94, A:\Princeton\Hist 465.94, 1994 Aug. (Box 241)